Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube channel Stock
Time. In this video, we
will talk about some such companies.
Today, big news is being seen in these companies. Among them,
we are talking about Maruti Suzuki, SBI Life,
PNC Infrastructure.
Apart from this, the
views of brokerage houses are also being seen in some companies like Lemon Hotel and Sun Pharmaceutical.
They have given breaking news and
also given target price. So, which companies
are these in the news? Before starting the discussion on this, I
would like to say that if
you have not subscribed to our channel,
please subscribe and also press the bell icon. So,
let's first talk about PNC
Infratech Limited. Today, a
little greenery was seen in it, but the
news in it is that the
company has received an order
for a highway project worth Rs 12060 crore from the National Highway Authority of India.
For this project, the company had
placed the lowest bid, due to which
it has got the order. Now, under this project, the company will work
on the six lane green field on the Varanasi Ranchi Kolkata Highway. Or the
company will
work on this highway from Pachmoon Village to Antarmashila Village.
Recently, the company has got 9  In March, the
company received two large orders
from NHAI, worth
2004 crores. The
company is getting large orders in both of these.
You can keep an eye on this as well because due to so many orders, this company has the
potential to grow in the future. If we
talk about its performance in the last 5 years, there is a decline of around 1%.
In one month, there is a decline of 14%.
In 6 months, there is a decline of around 1%. If we
talk about one year, there is a decline of 15%. If we
talk about the maximum, then there is a decline of 256%.
Now let's talk about Maruti Suzuki India
Limited, today there was a
decline in it too. Today the company's name
made a low of 8445, whereas its opening
was around 8544. News that
Suzuki Motor is seen increasing its stake in it is being
seen in the media. The news is that
between 10th and 15th March,
Suzuki Motor, the painting company of Maruti Suzuki, has bought shares.
345000 shares that he has bought
from the open market. Now
Suzuki Motor's stake in Maruti Suzuki has increased to
more than 56%, so
you can keep an eye on this as well.
If we look at the performance of its last 5 shares, there is a
decline of more than 0.5 percent.
Now let's talk about
seeing a decline of more than 1% in it today. The
news is that
approval has been given for a fundraise of Rs 269 crore 60 lakh in the name of the company.
This fund will be invested. So
you
can keep an eye on this as well. If we talk about the performance of its last 5 shares, there is a decline of
approximately 1.5%. There is a
decline of more than 11% in one month,
whereas only 4% is being seen in 6 months. So
this share can also remain in the red.
Now let's talk about the
performance of its last 5 shares, there is a
decline of 0.5 percent. There is a
slight decline in one month,
whereas in 6 months there is a decline of more than 9%.  A
decline of Rs. 102 is being seen. Now the news is
that the brokerage house has
kept its
target price on CLS and has told its target price as Rs. 102
which is
much higher than the current price of the city. The
CAGR of Lemon Tree Hotel is such that you should use your
brain, think and
study it, only after that take any
decision in this, you can keep an eye on this also. If we
talk about its one year performance in one day, then there is a
decline of 44%, whereas in the maximum
you can see that there is a decline of only 15% in it.
Now if we talk about G Electro
Plast, then today its
shares will see a decline of around 1.5%.
Now there is news that
this company is going to raise funds through IPO, that is, the
company will soon go for IPO,
such news is going on in the media,
so you can keep an eye on this also. If we
talk about its performance in the last 5 days, then there
is a decline of around 0.5%,
although there is a decline of more than 12% in 1 month and
more than 41% in 6 months.  Profits are being
seen. If we
talk about one year, then there is a maximum of 112%.
Or the company has given a profit of 3656% to
its investment, so you
can keep an eye on this as well. Talking about Sun
Pharmaceutical Industries Limited,
today there was a slight green in it,
although this company
also made a high of 963 today. Now the news is that
Jeffrey is optimistic about the company. He has
kept his bike and comment and its
target price at ₹1200. The
target price he has given is for the
next 12 months. So
keep this in mind. If we
talk about its performance in the last 5 months, there is a slight
green. In one month, there is a
decline of around 3.5%, whereas in 6 months there is a rise of
more than 9.30%. If we
talk about one year, there
is a green of 7.30%. In the maximum, this share has
given a profit of 42173% to its investment,
so you can also keep an eye on this in your
study.  According to, now let's talk about those
companies which have seen a huge decline today,
this is HDFC Life
Insurance Company, today this company has touched its 52
week low, it has made a new 52 week
low of
75 paise, this company has seen a
decline of more than 0.5 percent in its shares today,
it has
made its 52 week low, so you can keep an eye on this as well,
if we talk about ICC Prudential Life
Insurance Company, then
it is not behind HDFC Life in making a new 52 week low,
today it has also made its new 52 week low of
386,
although today a decline of almost 0.5 percent has been seen in its shares,
so you
can keep an eye on this as well, if we talk about it, then a
decline of 0.900% was seen in it today,
whereas if we talk about SBI Life Insurance, then it is being
seen today, so
these were some news we talked about today, do
not forget to tell us how you liked the video, along with
subscribing to our channel
and also press the bell icon, keep one thing in
mind that for any low news or any  Do
not invest in any stock based on the video or on the rating and target price of any brokerage house.
Before investing, know about its details
thoroughly, understand it, read about the
details of the company, then
you can invest as per your opinion. We
make this video on news only for knowledge purpose, so do
not invest in any stock based on this.
Thank you very much for watching the video.